cricketnmore.com 2019-12-22

# Privacy Policy at Cricketnmore

CRICKETNMORE is strongly committed to your right to privacy and to keeping your personal information secure. To earn your trust and confidence in our commitment, we are fully disclosing our privacy practices. CRICKETNMORE has the right to amend its privacy policy to suit the needs of the website and we will inform you about the updated regulations at the earliest possible time.  

**How we collect and use information**

CRICKETNMORE only collects the necessary personally identifiable information in order to respond to your requests for our customized products and services. Personally identifiable information includes, but is not limited to, first and last name, physical address, e-mail address, phone number, interests, birth date, and any other information that itself identifies or when tied to the above information, may identify you as a specific individual.

This website does not collect personally identifiable information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide it. CRICKETNMORE uses your personally identifiable information to operate the site and services and to inform you of new features, services.

When you visit cricketnmore.com, we may send one or more cookies a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets cricketnmore help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the site. A cookie may also convey information to us about how you use the website (e.g., the pages you view, the links you click and other actions you take on the site), and allow us to track your usage of cricketnmore.com over time. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your 

web browsers directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of cricketnmore.com may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.

Cricketnmore may disclose personally identifiable information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on the site or its owners; (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of the site owners, the site or the users of cricketnmore.com, and (iii) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of cricketnmore.com, the site, its owners, or the public.

**User/member interaction features**

cricketnmore.com has many features that provide for users/members to disclose their identities and communicate with other users/members. Your use of such features and disclosure of any personal details (e.g. e-mail address) by you through these features are at your sole risk and Cricketnmore accepts no responsibility for the same. However, if your privacy has been intruded as a result of participating in such features, you could notify us by e-mail at cricketnmore@gmail.com.

**Links to Other Websites**

The cricketnmore.com site contains links to other websites. Cricketnmore is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third partys site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit. We have no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party sites or services. 

**Notify Us**

If at any time you believe that cricketnmore.com or its users/members have not adhered to these principles, please notify Cricketnmore by e-mail at cricketnmore@gmail.com and we will use all commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and correct the problem.

**Your Content**

The freedom to write articles of your choice (sports) allows you to present your views to the visitors through this platform. However, the bloggers, writers and authors are advised not to violate the copyright laws meant to promote original work. The website will not be responsible for any content posted by its users. However, we will take appropriate action against copied content, if any, reported by a visitor.

The content on this website is published merely to enable sharing of ideas among people and to bring awareness about sports to the masses. The views expressed by the bloggers, authors or writers are their opinions and do not stand to be used as legal evidence.

**Google**

Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy. 

**We have implemented the following:**

Remarketing with Google AdSense

We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

**Our Key Advertising Partners**

Our key advertising partners are listed below. Click on their name to find out more and to opt-out from your data being used by them for OBA purposes.

**Colombia**

Our monetization partner Times Internet Ltd. are covered by the following [privacy policy](https://www.colombiaonline.com/privacy-policy)

**Bet365**

**Google**

**Tribal Fusion**

**The above privacy policy applies to all of Cricketnmore's platforms.**

**Client Support**

Cricketnmore Games Private Limited

FF-46, Narain Palace, Mangal Bazar Road, Laxmi Nagar

New Delhi - 110092
